PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

Our Company, Café RT Pvt Ltd (hereinafter referred to as“Aagam”) is a leading edtech company which strives to make everything easy when it comes to learning. In the process, Aagampledges to secure your trust in our company and in order to honor that trust, the Company adheres to ethical standards in gathering, using, and safeguarding the information you provide to us in anyform.

Café RT Pvt Ltd, under the brand name Aaagam, is a company incorporated in India for imparting learning in almost everysphere of education.

While using the Aagam’s Services, you (the user) are deemed tohave accepted the terms and conditions listed below. Aagam reserves the right to add, delete, alter or modify these terms and conditions carefully at any point of time. The User is there for eadvised to read these terms and conditions every time he/sheuses Aagam’s services. All products/services and information displayed on Aagam’s app/website or any other portal constitute an "invitation to offer". Your order for purchase constitutes your "offer" which shall be subject to the terms and conditions given below. Aagam reserves the right to accept or reject your offer. Please read carefully this privacy policy before using ourproducts/services.

Every user of our website/application must be in a position to provide an informed consent prior to providing any Information required for the use of the website/application. By registering with it, you are expressly consenting to its collection, processing, storing, disclosing and handling of your information as set forth in this Policy now and as amended by us. Processing, your information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining, sharing, transferring and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place inIndia. If you reside outside India your information will betransferred, processed and stored in accordance with the applicable data protection laws of India.

Your use of the Website/Application for registration or other wise through any mode including tablets or other storage/transmitting device shall signify your acceptance of this Policy and your agreement to be legally bound by the same. Your use of Aagam’s website/application in any electronic form or device shall bebound by the terms and conditions enumerated and agreed uponhereunder with willful and free consent.

If you wish not to agree with any of the terms and conditions of this Policy, kindly refrain from using the Website, Application or it sproducts.

User Provided Information
=========================

The Application/Website/services/products records the information you provide when you download and register on the Website/Application. When you register with us, you generally provide (a) your name, age, email address, phone number, password and your ward’s educational interests; (b) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, entercoupon code, respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us; (c) information you provide us when youcontact us for help; (d) information you enter into its system whenusing the website/application, such as while asking doubts,participating in discussions and taking mock tests etc. The said information collected from the users could be categorized as **“Personal Information“, “Sensitive Personal Information”** and “Associated Information“. Personal Information, Sensitive Personal Information and Associated Information (each asindividually defined under this Information Technology(Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 shall collectively bereferred to as **“Information”**n this Policy.

Aagam may use this Information to contact/update you from timeto time, to provide you with the services, important information, e-books, notes, required notices and marketing promotions. We will request you when it needs more information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you.

Aagam will not differentiate between who is using the device toaccess the website/application, so long as the log in/accesscredentials match with yours.

Aagam will, at all times, provide the option to you, not to providethe Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information, whichit seeks from you. Further, you can, at any time while using thewebsite/application, also have an option to withdraw your consentgiven earlier to it, to use such Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Information. Withdrawal of the consent by you isrequired to be sent in writing to us at the contact details providedin this Policy below. In any such event, Aagam fully reserves theright to withdraw further usage of the Application/Website orprovide any further Services/products thereunder to you.

Automatically Collected Information
===================================

In addition, the website/application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the typeof mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID,the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the website/application. As is true for most mobile applications, Aagam also collects other relevant information as per the permissions that you provide. Our Company uses an outside credit card processing company toraise invoices/bill you for the goods and services availed by you. These companies do notretain, share, store or use personally identifiable information of you for any other purpose.

Use of your Personal Information
================================

Aagam uses the collected Information to analyse trends, to conduct research, to administer the website/application, to learn about each user’s learning patterns and movements around thewebsite/application and products and to gather demographic information and usage behaviour about its user base as a whole. Aggregated and individual, anonymized and non-anonymized data may periodically be transmitted to external service providers tohelp us improve the website/application. Aagam will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described below in this Policy.

Aagam may use the individual data and behavior pattern scombined with personal information to provide you with personalized content, and better your learningobjectives/experience. Third parties provide certain serviceswhich we may use to analyze the data and information youprovide to personalize, drive insights and help it better yourexperience or reach out to you with more value addedapplications, products, information and services. However, thesethird party companies do not have any independent right to sharethis information.Aagam does not sell, trade or rent yourInformation to any third party unless, we have been expresslyauthorized by you either in writing or electronically to do so.Aagam may at times provide aggregate statistics about its customers, traffic patterns, and related site information toreputable third parties, however this information when disclosed will be in an aggregate form and does not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information. Aagam will occasionally send email notices or contact you to communicate about its services, as they are considered anessential part of the products/services you have chosen.

Aagam may disclose Information:

* as required by law, such as to comply with asubpoena/summon, or similar legal process;
* to enforce applicable terms & conditions, includinginvestigation of potential violations thereof;
* when it believes in good faith that the disclosure isnecessary to protect its rights, protect your safety or thesafety of others, investigate fraud, address security ortechnical issues or respond to a government request;
* to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property orsafety of the website/application or its users or the public asrequired or permitted by law;
* with third party service providers in order to personalize thewebsite/application for a better user experience and toperform behavioral analysis;
* to a third party that ensures same level of data protectionthat is adhered to by Aagam as provided in this policy.

Any portion of the Information containing personal data relating tominors provided by you shall be deemed to be given with theconsent of the minor’s legal guardian. Such consent is deemed tobe provided when you register with Aagam.

Access to your Personal Information
===================================

Aagam will provide you with the means to ensure that yourPersonal Information is correct and current. If you have filled out auser profile, it will provide an easy way for you to access andchange your profile from its website/application. Aagam adoptsstringent security measures to protect your password from beingexposed or disclosed to anyone. Only upon you forgetting the password, Aagam will have a right to reset the same to you withyour prior approval as per standard web practices.

Miscellaneous
=============

Cookies

Aagam send cookies (small files containing a string of characters)to your computer, thereby uniquely identifying your browser.Cookies are used to track your preferences, help you login faster,and aggregated to determine user trends. This data is used toimprove its offerings, such as providing more content in areas ofgreater interest to a majority of users. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you canreset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when acookie is being sent.

Links

Aagam may present links in a format that enables us to keeptrack of whether these links have been followed. Aagam uses thisinformation to improve its customized content. Clicking on linksmay take you to sites outside its domain. Aagam is notresponsible for the privacy practices of other web sites.

Alerts

Aagam may alert you by email or phone (through sms/call) toinform you about new services/products/promotions/coupons orother information which it perceives might be useful for you.

Sharing of information on Public Forums

When you use certain features on its website like the discussion forums and you post or share your personal information such ascomments, messages, files, photos, will be available to all users,and will be in the public domain. All such sharing of information isdone at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclosepersonal information in your profile including information as toschool, class, teachers etc. or when posting on its forums thisinformation may become publicly available.

Security

Aagam is concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality ofyour Information. Aagam provide physical, electronic, andprocedural safeguards to protect Information it processes andmaintain. An illustration being, Aagam limits access to thisInformation to authorized employees/agents only who need toknow that information in order to operate, develop or improve itswebsite/application. Please be aware that, although Aagam’sendeavour is to provide stringent security, for information itpossesses and maintains, no security system can prevent allpotential security breaches.

Currently, Aagam retains user data while an account is active andfor at least two years afterwards. It may alter this practiceaccording to legal and business requirements. For example, itmay lengthen the retention period for some data if needed tocomply with law or voluntary codes of conduct. Unless otherwiseprohibited, it may shorten the retention period for some types ofdata if needed to free up storage space.

Log information

When you access Aagam’s website/application, its servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, internet protocol address,browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

User communications

When you send an email or other communication to Aagam on itsdesignated email ID, website/application, it may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond toyour requests and improve our services.

Changes to this Statement

As the Company (Café RT Private Limited) evolves, its privacy policy will need to evolve as well to cover new situations. You areadvised to review this Policy regularly for any changes, ascontinued use is deemed approval of all changes.

Contact Information

Aagam operates its grievance cell which shall undertake all reasonable efforts to address your grievances at the earliest possible opportunity. You may contact at:

Grievance Officer:

Email ID: cafert.ott@gmail.com

Copyright © 2020 CafeRT. All rights reserved.

×

Login
-----

### As a Student

### As a Teacher

 REMEMBER ME [FORGOT PASSWORD?](https://aagamedu.com/password/reset)

OR

### Connect via Social Accounts

Login Login

### If you want to join us please inquire here

aagam
-----

×

Are you sure, you want to end this call?
----------------------------------------

* * *

Cancel

Yes

###### aagam

×

Please Sign up and [Become a Member](https://aagamedu.com/membership-plan).  
If you already have an account Please Login

OK

###### aagam

×

Thank you for registering with aagam.

OK

×

Message
-------

#### We need your Email address to complete the sign-up process!

×

SignIn
------

Send OTP

×

OTP Verify
----------

Verify

Resend

×

Create An Account
-----------------

As A
----

STUDENT

### Coming Soon

Close
